Zheng Qinwen never took her foot off it.
郑钦文始终没有松劲
And China has a finalist at the China Open for the first time.
中国球员首次闯进中网女单决赛
中国球员 第一次走进中网女单决赛
北京时间10月10日晚上
中网女单半决赛
郑钦文对阵梅尔滕斯
Oh, well, it's not going to be a fair fight.
噢 这可就难招架了
If Zheng's able to use that sort of finesse
如果郑钦文能拿出这种细腻手感
to go along with her power.
再配上她的力量
前4轮比赛 全部打到第三盘
半决赛首盘 郑钦文3比0开局
4比1的优势被追到4比4
郑钦文发球
她从底线压向网前 保住发球局
She gets it done.
她拿下了这一分
Winners number 12, 13, 14 and 15
第十二至十五记制胜分
in this opening set.
都是在这第一盘里
5比5之后 她连赢两局
7比5收下首盘
And the mishit from Mertens,
梅尔滕斯这一拍打偏了
and Zheng Qinwen delights the Beijing faithful.
郑钦文让北京球迷欢呼
It looked like it was going to be a beatdown
原以为会是一边倒
in the opening 15, 16 minutes.
在开头十五六分钟的时候
It turned out to be anything but.
结果却完全不是这样
But in the end, the Queen comes through in her court
最终 女王在主场闯过这一关
and has a one-set lead in semifinal number two.
在第二场半决赛中先赢一盘
第二盘 接发后在底线连续回击
反复把球送向对手反手侧 率先破发
And even more dominant start to the set than it was in the first.
这一盘的开局比第一盘更强势
2比0时 她救下一次破发点
保住领先
现在再保发 优势来到5比2
Oh, that'll seal the deal on a 5-2 lead.
这一拍锁定了五比二的领先
And Zheng Qinwen wakes up the crowd once again in Beijing.
郑钦文又一次点燃了北京的观众
全场32记制胜分
8记直接发球得分
第一发球得分率88%
决赛对阵安德烈耶娃
郑钦文能在主场捧杯吗？
And in the end, Elise Mertens ran out of gas.
到了最后 梅尔滕斯有些后劲不足了
Zheng Qinwen never took her foot off it.
郑钦文始终没有松劲
And China has a finalist at the China Open for the first time.
中国球员首次闯进中网女单决赛
Another quality win for Zheng Qinwen as she topples a top-20 opponent.
又一场胜利 她击败世界前二十
And she is to the last day of this WTA 1000 event in the Chinese capital.
她将登上北京一千赛的决赛舞台